## **BRITTANI** COURT

Richmond, VA
Phone: 4342829875
Email: bcourt95@gmail.com

LinkedIn: http://www.linkdin.com/in/thanksfrom3rittani/ GitHub: http://github.com/Serendipbrity?tab=repositories | Portfolio: https://serendipbrity.github.io/portfolio2022/

#### SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with 3 years of background in Information Technology. Effective at considering most aspects of user experience when designing. Self taught prior to earning a Full Stack Web Development Certificate from the University of Richmond.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Git, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, AJAX, React, APIs, the DOM, JSON, Node, ES6, OOP, Express, MySQL, MVC paradigm, Sequelize, Testing, PWA, MongoDB, NoSQL, GraphQL, MERN stack

## **P**ROJECTS

## **Gators Newsletter**

**Link to GitHub:** https://github.com/Serendipbrity/Gators-Newsletter/ **Link to Deployed Project:** https://serendipbrity.github.io/Gators-Newsletter/

- **Description:** An elementary school newsletter where parents can more easily keep up to date with their child's school events/announcements. They can also use it to inform the school of absences.
  - Core responsibilities: Page layout/design. Functionalities. Project set up. Task management.
    - Tools / languages used: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Git, UIKit, APIs, Bootstrap

## **Belize National Fire Station**

Link to GitHub: https://github.com/ppeppin34/fire-dept/

Link to Deployed Project: https://belize-fire-dept.herokuapp.com/

- **Description:** A website to help the Belize National Fire Stations keep track of/update their employees. You can search employees by fire station.
- Core responsibilities: Page layout/design. Functionalities. Project set up. Task management.
- Tools / languages used: Handlebars, Sequelize, Node, Express, Dotenv, MySQL, UlKit, Bootstrap, Sessions. bcrypt

### **EDUCATION**

## Degree or Certification: Full Stack Web Development University of Richmond

High School Diploma: Fort Hill High School 2013

#### EXPERIENCE

# Teaching Assistant 2U/EdX (Front End Web Development)

United Kingdom (Remote)

Assist in teaching Front End Web Development. Help students with understanding topics and debugging projects. Plan for successful classes.

## Delivery Driver Amazon Flex

Richmond, VA

2021-Current

2022-Current

Pick up and drop off customers safely to their destinations. Provide friendly customer service.

# Delivery Driver Pierce Logistics (Amazon)

Richmond, VA

Delivered over 200 stops a day. DOT licensed to drive box trucks. In field customer server. Safely navigated through high pressure environments. Followed scanning, tracking and documentation procedures. Lifted up to 50 pounds per package.

## Solar Sales Consultant High Desert Energy

Phoenix, AZ

2017-2019

Discussed electrical requirements, site conditions, price and other factors to assist customers.

Assessed customer energy needs and provided individualized product recommendations. Enhanced customer satisfaction with fast, knowledgeable service.

Helped in a team to handle high volume work by prioritizing tasks and organizing supplies.

2019-2021

#### **Head Server** 2014-2017 Kabuki Japanese Steakhouse

Christiansburg, VA

Used time management to deliver efficient service. Followed satey, sanitation and food handling guidelines. Processed payments. Communicated with team to ensure smooth group efforts. Satisfied customers with fast, friendly and knowledgeable support.

**Student Worker** 2011-2013

**Food and Drug Administration** 

Cumberland, MD

Supported proper business operations by preparing and processing documentation. Protected organization in event of emergencies with well planned crisis management strategies.

Identified and addressed business vulnerabilities in areas governing asset protection and physical security.